Undergraduate Education, Office of the Vice Provost for; Records ua510
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Dean of Undergraduate Studies (Kim, Scatton, Pipkin), 1978-1997; 1985-1995; 4; 4.2 cubic ft.
  This series consists of records created by the Office of the Dean of Undergraduate Studies. The bulk of the materials in this series were created between 1988 and 1995, when the position of Dean was held by Sung Bok Kim (except for an interim period in 1991 and 1992 when the position was held by Ernest Scatton). Also included are a few materials created during the tenures of Sung Bok Kim's predecessor, Harry Hamilton, and successor, John Pipkin.
  Topics in this series include: enrollment management, planning for freshman orientation, scholarship and fellowship planning, correspondence with academic and administrative departments, planning for the Undergraduate Bulletin, faculty policies, selection of the Excellence in Teaching Awards, and a variety of short-term committees and task forces.
  - 4x4, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Advisement Services Center/Undergraduate Studies, 1993; 1994; 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Albany Law School, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Albany Semester Program, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Albany Student Press, 1991; 1992 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Alpha Chi, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alumni Association, 1991; 1992; 1994 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - American Council on Education - Center for Leadership Development, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Annual Physical Inventory, 1987; 1988; 1989; 1993 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Annual Report for Undergraduate Office, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Annual Review, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Articulation Agreements, 1987-1994 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Articulation Agreements - 3/2 Engineering Programs, 1988-1991; 1993 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Articulation Agreements - Ford Foundation, 1987; 1988; 1990; 1991 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Arts and Science Curriculum Council, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Arts and Sciences Deans-SUNY, 1991; 1992; 1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Arts and Sciences Reorganization, 1991; 1992 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - ASD/SIRS, 1988; 1989; 1990 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Asian/Pacific American Student Conference, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Assessment, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Assessment, 1992; Undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Assessment Recommendations, Undated (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Association for General and Liberal Studies, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Athletic Program, 1994 June (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Audit Information, 1993; 1994; Undated (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Awards for Teaching and Advising, 1991 September (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Awards, Scholarships, and Fellowships, 1989; 1991; 1992; 1993 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - B.A/M.A Program, 1988; 1989; 1990 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Belgrade, University of, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Benjamin and David Scharps Prize, 1989; 1990; 1992 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Black Issues in Higher Education, 1991; 1992 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Board of Trustees, 1991; 1992; 1993 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Board of Trustees Visit, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Bookstore - Textbook Orders, 1994; 1995 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Budget, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Budget Panel, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Bulletin - Gopher Structure, Undated (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Bulletin Information, 1988; 1989; 1990; 1993 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Captial Campaign Program Proposals, Academic Affairs, 1989 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Capping and Restricting Majors, 1993; 1995 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Campus Alcohol Policy, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Campus Commission on Co-Curricular Dimensions of the Freshman Year, 1988; 1989; 1990 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Campus Life, 1991; 1992; 1993 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Campus Planning Process, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Campus Safety, 1992; 1994 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Campus Safety Survey, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Campus Voluntary Leave Program, 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Career Development Center, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Center for Excellence in Teaching and Learning, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - Chancellor's Commission on Diversity and Pluralism, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - Childern's Literature Course Offerings, 1991; 1992 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - Citizen's Scholarship Foundation of America, 1995 June 15 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Coalition for a Just Community, 1990; 1991 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Co-Curricular Commission on the Freshman Year: Report and Recommendtions, 1990 March 19 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Co-Curricular Committee, 1993; 1994; Undated (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Co-Curricular Committee, 1994; 1995; Undated (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - College Board, 1991; 1992; 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - College Entry - Level Knowledge and Skills, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - College of Optometry, 1987; 1990; Undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Collegiate Interfaith Center, 1990; 1992 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - College Level Examination Program(CLEP), 1991-1992 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Committee on Academic Standing, 1992; 1994 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Committee on Advising Campus-Wide, 1991; 1992 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Committee to Review Correspondence, 1994 June 9 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Community Colleges, 1993; 1994 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Community Service, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Community Service Internship, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Complaints, 1994 February 2 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - Computing Allocation, 1993; 1994 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - Computing Center, 1988-1994; 1996 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Computers and Colonial Quad, 1992; 1993 (Box 1, Folder 71)
  - Computer Specifications, Undated (Box 1, Folder 72)
  - Computer Usage, 1995; 1996 (Box 1, Folder 73)
  - Comshare User Meeting, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 74)
  - Conference on Multiculturalism, 1991 (Box 1, Folder 75)
  - Controller, Office of the, 1989; 1990; 1991; 1993 (Box 1, Folder 76)
  - Conversations in the Disciplines, 1991; 1992; 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 77)
  - Conversations in the Disciplines, 1993; 1994 (Box 1, Folder 78)
  - Coordinator of Academic Support and Program Development for Learning Disabled Student, 1991; 1992 (Box 1, Folder 79)
  - Couseling Services, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 80)
  - Counterfeit Letters and Notices, 1991; 1992; 1993; Undated (Box 1, Folder 81)
  - Course Offerings by Departmennt, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 82)
  - Cross Registration, 1991; 1992; 1993 (Box 1, Folder 83)
  - Data-General Undergraduate Students, 1987-1991; Undated (Box 1, Folder 84)
  - Dean Search Committees, 1989; 1994; Undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Deans, Department Chairs, and Program Directors-Listing, 1991 September 12 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Deans List, 1985; 1989-1992; 1994 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Deans List, 1992; 1993; 1995; 1996 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Deans List, 1996; 1997 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Dean of Undergraduate Studies, 1986; 1987; Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Departmental Profiles, 1989; 1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Departmental Profiles, 1991; 1994 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Departmental Profiles, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Deregistration Policy, 1992; 1993 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - DIFR Advisory Committee, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Disabled Students Services, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Dissertation Completion Program, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Diversity Conference, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Division I Athletics, 1990; 1993 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Doctoral Program Review, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Dutch Studies, 1994; Undated (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Easter Holiday, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Education Title 3, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Educational Leadership Corps Program, 1993 May 3 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Educational Opportunity Program, 1994; 1995 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Ellis Hospital School of Nursing, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Empire State (Scholarships,etc.), 1988-1992 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Employee Programs/Information, 1988; 1991; 1992 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Employee Relations Update, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Enrollment Initiatives, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Enrollment Management, 1994; 1995; Undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Enrollment Management Committee, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Enrollment Management Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Enrollment Management Committee, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Enrollment Trends, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Environment Studies, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - EOP Newsletters, 1989-1994 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Equipment Management, 1994; 1995 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Ethics Disclosure Statements, 1992 June 19 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Ethics in Government Act, 1989 March (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Excellence in Teaching Award, 1989; 1990 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Excellence in Teaching Award, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Excellence in Teaching Award, 1991; 1992; 1995 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Excellence in Teaching Award, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Excellence in Teaching Award, 1992; 1993 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Excellence in Teaching Award, 1993; 1994 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Excellence in Teaching Award, 1993; 1994; Undated (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Excellence in Teaching Award, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Excellence in Teaching Award, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Excellence in Teaching Award, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Excellence in Teaching Committee, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Expanded Early Warning For Freshman, 1992 April 27 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - FACT Scholarships, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Faculty Advisement Volunteers, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Faculty Breakfast, 1990; 1991 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Faculty Fair, 1993; 1995 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Faculty Forum, 1994 March 31 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Faculty Mentor Program, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Faculty Mentor Program, 1988-1994; Undated (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Faculty Office Hours, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 56)
  - Faculty Office Hours, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 57)
  - New Faculty Orientation Program, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 58)
  - Faculty Participants, 1994 March 30 (Box 2, Folder 59)
  - Faculty Recruitment, 1989; 1991 (Box 2, Folder 60)
  - Faculty Resident Search, 1988; 1989; 1991 (Box 2, Folder 61)
  - Faculty Resident Search, 1991; 1992 (Box 2, Folder 62)
  - Faculty Resident Search, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 63)
  - Faculty Resident Search, 1994; 1995 (Box 2, Folder 64)
  - Faculty Residents, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 65)
  - Faculty Residents/Associates, 1988; 1989; 1990 (Box 2, Folder 66)
  - Faculty Residents/Associates, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 67)
  - Faculty Residents/Associates, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 68)
  - Faculty Residents/Associates, 1991-1994 (Box 2, Folder 69)
  - Family Residents/Associates, 1994; 1995 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Faculty Residents Meetings, 1992; 1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Faculty Workload, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Fall 1992 Action (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Fall 1992 Course Schedule, 1992 January 7 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Fall Orientation, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Fall Orientation, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Fall Orientation, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Finance and Business, 1990; 1991; 1992; 1994 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Financial Aid, 1992; 1993; 1994 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - FIPSE Grant, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Five-Year Planning, 1988 August 25 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Foreign Graduate Students and English, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Foreign Language Requirements, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Fossieck Lecture Series, 1989; 1990 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Foundation for Economic Education, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Freshman Assembly, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Freshman Assembly - Juan Williams, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Freshman Assembly-Linda Hogan, 1990; 1991; 1992 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Freshman Book Workshop, 1993; 1994 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Freshman Orientation-Garry Wills, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Freshman Orientation Seminar, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Freshman Summer Reading Program, 1988; Undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Freshman Summer Reading Program, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Freshman Summer Reading Program, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Freshman Summer Reading Program, 1991; 1992; 1993; 1994 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Freshman Summer Reading Program, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Freshman Summer Reading Program - Faculty Facilitators, 1991; 1992; 1993 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Freshman Year Experience, 1992; 1995 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - General Education Honors Program, 1988; 1990; 1992; 1993; 1994 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - General Education Honors Program, 1993; 1994 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - General Education Honors Program, 1993; 1994 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - General Education Honors Program Faculty, 1988-1992 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - General Education Proposal, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - General Studies, 1991; 1992; 1994; 1995 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - General Studies Freeze, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - German, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Gladys Brooks Endowed Scholarship Fund, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Golden Apple Award, 1989; 1990 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Golden Key, 1990; 1991; 1992; 1993 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Governor's' Conference on Library and Information Services, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Graduate Studies, 1991; 1992; 1993 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Guilderland High School (S.U.P.A), 1990-1997 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Health and Counseling Services, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Human Resources Management, 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Information Systems and Technology, 1987-1991; 1993 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Institutional Profile, Undated (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - International Programs, 1988; 1989; 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - Judicial Affairs, Undated (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Lewis Mumford Center, 1989; 1991 (Box 3, Folder 51)
  - Liberty Scholarship, 1988; 1990 (Box 3, Folder 52)
  - MACCC, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 53)
  - Major and Minor Advisement Fair, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Mathematics and Statistics, 1987-1991 (Box 3, Folder 55)
  - May Department Store Fund, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 56)
  - Minority Enrollment, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 57)
  - Multi-Cultural Concerns Committee, 1988; 1989; 1990 (Box 3, Folder 58)
  - National Merit Scholarship, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 59)
  - Office for Research, 1991; 1992 (Box 3, Folder 60)
  - Office of Institutional Research, 1991; 1992 (Box 3, Folder 61)
  - Office of the President, 1991; 1992; 1993; 1994 (Box 3, Folder 62)
  - Orientation(January 1989), 1988 December 5 (Box 3, Folder 63)
  - Orientation Programs for New Faculty and Teaching Assistants, 1987; 1988 (Box 3, Folder 64)
  - Orientation Programs for New Faculty and Teaching Assistants, 1987; 1988; 1989 (Box 3, Folder 65)
  - Parents Weekend Planning Committee, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 66)
  - Part-Time Faculty Budget, 1986; 1988; Undated (Box 3, Folder 67)
  - Personnel, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 68)
  - Phi Beta Kappa, 1989 April 5 (Box 3, Folder 69)
  - Physical Education, 1989; 1992; 1994; Undated (Box 3, Folder 70)
  - Physical Plant, 1988-1993; 1995 (Box 3, Folder 71)
  - Physics, 1987; 1988 (Box 3, Folder 72)
  - Physics-Applied Physics, 1987; 1988 (Box 3, Folder 73)
  - Planning Meeting-Presidents Ofice, 1988 July 7 (Box 3, Folder 74)
  - Political Science, 1988; 1990 (Box 3, Folder 75)
  - Pre-Health Advisory Committee, 1995 (Box 3, Folder 76)
  - Pre-Health Association, 1990 February 28 (Box 3, Folder 77)
  - Presidential Awards For Undergraduate Research, 1986; 1989 (Box 3, Folder 78)
  - Presidential Fellowships, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 79)
  - Presidental Scholars Selection Committee, 1987; 1991; 1992 (Box 3, Folder 80)
  - Programs and Priorites, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 81)
  - Psychology, 1988-1991 (Box 3, Folder 82)
  - Purchasing, 1988-1994 (Box 3, Folder 83)
  - Registrar, Adiministrative Calendars, 1991-1994 (Box 3, Folder 84)
  - Registrar, Advisory Committee, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 85)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 1987; 1988 (Box 3, Folder 86)
  - Reorganization, 1988; Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Residential Life, 1991-1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Resource Management Group, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Reviews of Programs, 1987; 1988; 1989 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Scholarship Committee, 1988; 1989 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Scholarship and Fellowship, 1990 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Scholarship and Fellowship, 1991-1992 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Scholarship and Fellowships, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Scholarship and Fellowships, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Search Committee for Vice President for Student Affairs, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - SIRS, 1987; 1988 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Social and Behavioral Sciences, 1984; 1985; 1987; 1988; 1989 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Sociology, 1988; 1989; 1990; 1991 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Soviet Students, 1988 December 22 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - State Education Department Audit, 1987; 1988 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Statistics Courses, 1987 November (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Gregory Stevens, Assistant Dean, College of Humanities and Fine Arts, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Student Accounts, 1989; 1992; 1993 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Student Affairs, 1987; 1989 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Student Affairs, 1991; 1992; 1993 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Student Association, 1988-1991 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Student Association, 1988; 1989; 1990; 1992; 1995 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Students at Risk, 1986; 1987; 1988 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - "Students At Risk" Committee, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Summer Session Admissions, 1987-1990 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - SUNYA Capital Region Consortium - Chief Academic Officers, 1991-1995 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - SUNYA Capital Region Faculty Development Project Steering Committee, 1990 March 15 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - SUNY Cobleskill, 1991; 1994 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - SUNY Consortion Deans, 1987; 1988 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Survey of Recent Graduates, 1984; 1985; 1990; 1991 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Symbolics Committee, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Talented Student Admissions Program, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Target of Opportunity Program, 1987 October 30 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Teacher Education Program - General Education and Writing, 1989; Undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - Teacher Education - Program Review, 1985; 1987; 1989; 1990; Undated (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Teaching, 1978; 1987; 1988; 1989 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Teaching Evaluation, 1985; 1988; 1989; 1990 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Telephone Service, 1989; 1990; 1991; 1994 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Transfer Affairs Subcommittee Minutes, 1990 January 23 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - Undergraduate Advisory Group, 1987; 1988 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - Undergraduate Education(Freshman) Report, 1987; 1989; Undated (Box 4, Folder 41)
  - Undergraduate Education, miscellaneous, 1985-1988 (Box 4, Folder 42)
  - Undergraduate Education-"New Liberal Arts" Program, 1982-1984; 1986-1988 (Box 4, Folder 43)
  - Undergraduate Policy Reminders, 1988; 1989 (Box 4, Folder 44)
  - Undergraduate Programs Registration, 1989; Undated (Box 4, Folder 45)
  - Undergraduate Retention Subcommittee, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 46)
  - Undergraduate Scholarships, 1987; 1988; 1989 (Box 4, Folder 47)
  - Undergraduate Studies, 1988; 1990; 1994; 1995 (Box 4, Folder 48)
  - Undergraduate Studies Agendas and Projects, 1987; 1988 (Box 4, Folder 49)
  - United University Professions Meetings, 1991; 1992 (Box 4, Folder 50)
  - University Council Retreat, 1991 (Box 4, Folder 51)
  - University Adcancement, 1990; 1991; 1992 (Box 4, Folder 52)
  - University Library, 1991; 1992; 1994 (Box 4, Folder 53)
  - University Relations, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 54)
  - University Seminar on Oriental Religions, 1989 March 20 (Box 4, Folder 55)
  - University Senate, 1989-1992 (Box 4, Folder 56)
  - University Senate, 1991; 1992; 1993 (Box 4, Folder 57)
  - University Senate, 1992; 1993 (Box 4, Folder 58)
  - Video Study Guides, 1988 March 5 (Box 4, Folder 59)
  - Work Load, 1988; 1989 (Box 4, Folder 60)
  - World Cultures Subcommittee, 1987 October 6 (Box 4, Folder 61)
  - World Week Coordinating Committee, 1988-1992 (Box 4, Folder 62)
  - Writing Center, 1987; 1988; 1989; Undated (Box 4, Folder 63)
  - Writing - Intensive Program, 1987; 1988; 1989; 1991 (Box 4, Folder 64)
  - Budget and Planning, 1987; 1988; Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Registration (Fall 1989) (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Project Renaissance, 1995-2007; 1995-2000; 5; 0.33 cubic ft.
  This series documents the development, implementation, and periodic review of Project Renaissance, which was a living-learning program for first year students at the University that ran from 1996 to 2011. The series contains documentation of the grant application process, annual reports, and related correspondence.
  - Grant Guidelines, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Program Proposal, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence, 1995-1998 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Interim Memorandum on Evaluation of Project Renaissance, 1996 December (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Annual Report, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Annual Report, 1997 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Program Information (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Program Information (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Year One Evaluation, ca. 1997 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Year Two Evaluation, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Interim Report: Year III, ca. 1998 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Program Information, 1998; 1999 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - State Account Reports, 2000; 2001 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Historical Information, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Program Review, 2007 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Project Renissance: A Proposal, Undated (Box 1, Folder 16)